Guide to the Mark Kulstad Academic Papers, 1971-2015 UA 385
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Mark Kulstad academic papers
1971-2021
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Kulstad, Mark
UA 385
18 Linear Feet 28 boxes
The academic papers of Mark Kulstad contain hand-written notes from his graduate studies, hand-written comments on his drafts of published articles on Leibniz, Spinoza, Descartes and Locke, his published articles on Leibniz, Spinoza, and Descartes, his hand-written notes from History of Philosophy conferences, and student's hand-written evaluations of his work at Rice.
Biographical / Historical
Mark Kulstad is a well rounded scholar of Philosophy born on January 8, 1947. His undergraduate degree spanned the years 1965 to 1969. He was awarded cum laude with the highest distinction at the conclusion of his undergraduate studies. His graduate studies were completed in 1975 at The University of Michigan. His thesis topic was Leibniz's Doctrine of Pre-established Harmony.
After his studies and the job hunting process he came to Rice. During the job hunting process he applied to many places including Duke and The University of Notre Dame. He was first admitted as an assistant professor at Rice on July 1, 1975 with a 3-year extension in 1978. He was reappointed this status again in 1981 for a year. He was then appointed associate professor in 1981. He became an full professor in 1986. He was the chair of the philosophy department from 1988 to 1992. His research interests center around Leibniz. He was given the recognition of the Alexander von Humboldt Foundation research fellow in Hanover, West Germany in 1979 to 1980 working in the Leibniz archive. His interest in Leibniz extended to his presidency in the Leibniz Society of North America from 1981- 1983. He took up this role again in the years 2002- 2006. He also took his interest in Leibniz to conferences and he arranged a conference about Leibniz, "The International Young Leibniz Conference" at Rice. He also organized the First Annual North American Leibniz Society for the year 2008 at Rice. During his time at Rice he was heavily involved with Graduate Admissions, Graduate Seminars, and Hanszen College as a faculty associate for the years 1978-1979,1982-1983,and 1983-1984.
Scope and Contents
Throughout Mark Kulstad's philosophical career he has focused on publications, conferences, talks, and his teaching. The collection as a whole displays his cohesive contributions to the academic community at both Rice University and The University of Michigan. His research on Leibniz, Spinoza, and Descartes is displayed throughout the entirety of the collection, and gives a deeper look into his endeavors in the scholarship of Leibniz. The collection contains extensive information on Kulstad's involvement in the Leibniz Essay Competition, the Leibniz society and its related conferences, and on his publications on the subject. The collection also has some highlights of photos and his hand written drafts of his research papers. There is also an extensive amount of information about his time at The University of Michigan as a graduate student. The first series of the collection highlights his course notes as well as his academic papers, his search for jobs, and his route to becoming a full professor with tenure. There is also a look into his thesis preparation and is accompanied by his finished thesis. The next section focuses on his involvement at Rice University. Kulstad was very involved at Rice and the collection emphasizes his time as a faculty associate at Hanszen College, his involvement as a graduate admissions advisor, and as a graduate seminar teacher. In Series I Biographical: The series showcases a well rounded representation of Kulstad's course work from his Graduate studies at The University of Michigan. This series includes: class notes, course notebooks, course papers, and his thesis and the accompanying drafts. In Series II Professional Development: The series includes his involvement with committees, as well as the societies and workshops he worked hard to support. There is also an accurate representation of the conferences he attended as well as the lectures he gave. In Series III Graduate Seminars and Admissions: The series highlights the Graduate Seminars Kulstad conducted. There is also coverage of his time as part of the Graduate admissions committee. In Series IV Course Material: This series highlights the classes that Kulstad taught at Rice. The information included includes course outlines, course readings, and course examinations requirements. There is also information about the classes that Kulstad audited. In Series V Research: This series emphasizes Kulstad's research on Spinoza and Leibniz. This section includes readings on these topics as well as comments, information about the grants he applied for and the materials he requested for his research. There is also information about the publishers he was involved with. Series VI Publications: This series focuses on his drafts and publications. Noteworthy publications are Leibniz, animals, and Apperception, as well as Leibniz's Conception of Expression.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research. Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Mark Kulstad donated the papers on June 29, 2016 with an addendum on August 24, 2016.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges; Philosophy, German; Philosophy, Modern; Education
Document Types
lecture notes; publications
Places
Internationaler Leibniz-Kongress
- Series I: Biographical, 1966-2015 (Box 1-4)
  - Course material, 1966-2009 (Box 1)
    - Union City School Papers (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - University of Michigan, handouts, class notes for Metaphysics + Phil Psych., 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - University of Michigan, Course 462 British Empiricists, 1966-1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - College Philosophy papers/ notes, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Contemporary Ethics, 1968-05-13 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Theory of Knowledge, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Theory of Knowledge 477, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - University of Michigan course papers, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 414 Logic I, 460 Medieval, 570 Moralists, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Dr. Frankena- Topics in History Ethics- 570-001, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - University of Michigan course spiral, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Ethics Preliminary Philosophy 361, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Ancient Philosophy 388+ 501 and miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Ancient Philsophy, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Russell and Quine, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Franken 640 Ethics, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Official status at Michigan, 1972-08-31-1974-07-17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Professor Fred Feldman 461 Continental Realism (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Philosophy of Science (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - University of Michigan 17th and 18th Century Winter, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Winter Course, University of Michigan Phil 420 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 389 (Wood); 461 (Feldman) Aims of Philosophy misc., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - University of Michigan relevant to CV, 1977-2009 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - University of Michigan Course papers (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Job seeking, thesis, and tenure process, 1971-2015 (Box 2)
    - Materials relating to job hunting, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Job seeking, University of Michigan (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Job possibilities (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Rough writing for thesis (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Thesis draft, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Fred's comments [on thesis] (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Copy of doctoral dissertation of Professor Mark Kulstad, "Leibniz's Expression Thesis", 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Rice, 1971-1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Department history, 1975-1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Comprehensive History of Department, 1977-2010 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Kolenda papers (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Important Philsophy Department job candidates (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Official status at Rice, 1976-2015 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Summer research grant application reports, etc., 1976-1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Annual Reports, 1977-1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Vitae, 1981-2005 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Summer assistants, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - "Putting the Pieces together"- resource for tenure (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Tenure, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Grandy support letter, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - APA E., 1992 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Meeting with Dick + George, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Official full professor criteria (Gnit MAK), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - University Council file, promotion without tenure (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - First draft of full professor criteria with comments, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Full professor memos + letters, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Material submitted for full professor position in the Fall, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Reports to chair/ re: salary evaluation, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Texas A&M etc., 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - MAK full professor, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Full professor status correspondence, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Full professor review memos, 1994-08 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Full professor: key meeting with George Ssner (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Curriculum Vitae, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Full professor success, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Full professor promotion Mtls (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Official status in profession, Leibniz award, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Status at Rice, 1980-2015 (Box 3)
    - Hanszen advisees, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Hanszen material, 1981-1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Hanszen College, Faculty Associate, 1984-1988 (Box 3, Folder 4-7)
    - Hanszen College, Faculty Advisor, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 8-12)
    - Hanszen College, Faculty Advisor, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
    - Hanszen College, Faculty Advisor, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 15-19)
    - Rice University Newcomers Guide, 2006-2008 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Rice University Newcomer's Guide, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Hanszen College, Faculty Advisor, 2012-2013 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - New Student Look book, 2012-2015 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - List of students (Brown) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Contract work, 1990-2005 (Box 3-4)
    - Russell's Multiple Relation Theory, HPQ, History of Philosophy Quarterly Reviews, 1990-05 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - PH and PHR Referee job: "The Substance of Leibniz's Substance", 1992 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - "Leibniz on Divine Foreknowledge of Future Contingents and Human Freedom", 1993-02 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - History of Philosophy Quarterly Reviews, 1993-05-26-1993-08-09 (Box 3, Folder 28-31)
    - History of Philsophy Quarterly Reviews, 1994-02-03-1994-12-18 (Box 3, Folder 32-37)
    - History of Philosophy Quarterly Reviews, 1995-02-09 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Nous "Haeccetism and Anti-Haeccetism in Leibniz's Philosophy" (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Southwest Philosophy Review "Leibniz: There are no extrinsic denominations", 1995-03-30 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - "The Co.Extensiveness of the Attributes in Spinoza", 1995-10-31 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - "Leibniz on the Union of Body + Soul", 1995-11-13 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - History of Philosophy Quarterly "Descartes Unknown Faculties and Incurable Doubt in 399", 1996-05-09 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - History of Philosophy Quarterly Reviews, 1997-06-18-1997-12-21 (Box 3, Folder 44-48)
    - History of Philosophy Quarterly Reviews #4 441 "Descartes and the Lucid Dream" reject, 1996-09-11 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Southwest, Philosophy Review "Cartesian Doubt + Divine Omnipotence: The Search for Descartes' God.", 1997-07-10 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - History of Philosophy Quarterly Reviews, " Spinoza on the Immortality of the Soul, Mind", 1998-08-07 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - "Mind- Body Dualism and the Biopsychosocial model of pain: What did Descartes really say?, 1998-08-21 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - History of Philosophy Quarterly Reviews, 1999-05-07-1999-06 (Box 3, Folder 53-55)
    - History of Philosophy Quarterly Reviews, 2000-06-2000-07 (Box 3, Folder 56-58)
    - JHI "Looking for Leibniz's Metaphysics", 2000-08-07 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - History of Philosophy Quarterly Reviews, "The Moand Embodied: Leibniz's Hylomorphism and its Influence in 18th Century Life Science", 2001-02 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - "Contingentia Mundi: Leibniz Rev. Negative", 2001-05 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - History of Philosophy Quarterly Reviews, 2002-02-08-2002-12 (Box 3, Folder 62-64)
    - Enigma of Cartesian Infinite: Levinas/Mariors Reviewed for Steve Crowell, 2002-06-17 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Synthese Soft Reduction of Extrinsic Denominations reject, 2002-06-17 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - AFGP: Leibniz on Middle Knowledge accept, 2002-06-17 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - "Animal Reproduction and the Metaphysics of Cause in Early Modern Thought", 2003-05 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - JHP "Leibniz's Argument for Primitive Concepts", 2002-10 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - HPQ, History of Philsophy Quarterly Reviews, "Leibniz: Microscopy, Cs. Immortality", 2004 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Referee job: "Concept and Substance In Leibniz Metaphysics accept, revisions JHP, 2005-02-20 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - History Philosophy Quarterly Reviews, no date (Box 4, Folder 3,4)
    - Locke newsletter and Leibniz and Malebranche on innate ideas (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - History Philosophy Quarterly Reviews, correspondence (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Nous Philosophy Matter, Hartz (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Leibniz's Foundational Strategies + Ideal of Consistency. JHP (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - "Representation in Leibniz's Theory of Sensation + Thought" (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Other journals (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - JHP referee correspondence (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Duchesneau (Box 4, Folder 12,13)
    - Reference job "Lebniz and Individual"/ Yed Tepe (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - "Leibnizian Chronadology: Monads, Chronads, and Time" no formal review (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Susan Peppers - Bates Papers (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - The Philosophical Review (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Referee job: Marc Elliot Bobro's manuscript, "Self and Substance in Leibniz" (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Nicholas Jolley book review by Mark A. Kulstad (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Series II: Professional Development, 1981-2014 (Box 4-11)
  - Committees, Seminars, Workshops, Societies, 1982-2014 (Box 4-8)
    - Undergraduate Teaching Committee, 1982-1987 (Box 4, Folder 20-28)
    - Scientia, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 46-48)
    - Faculty Committee, 1986-01-21-1987 (Box 4, Folder 49-62)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 1-6)
    - Library Committee, 1988-10-24-1992 (Box 5, Folder 7-27)
    - Friends of Fondren (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - George R. Brown Teaching Awards (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - The Cain Project, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 30-33)
    - Computer committee (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Epist Seminar, Grady, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - NEH Seminar, 1988-2003-07-02 (Box 5, Folder 36-42)
    - NEH Seminar, 2003-07-07-2004 (Box 5, Folder 43-57)
    - NEH Summer Institute (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
    - Structural Explanation (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Intentionality in the Arnauld- Malebranche Debate Nadler (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Leibniz's Theory of Counterfactuals by Reginald (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - NEH Seminar (Box 6, Folder 7-11)
    - Des Flosses Correspondence Engl. Rutherford + Look + De Volder correspondence Engl. Lodge (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - NEH summer seminar (Box 6, Folder 13,14)
    - Rice Seminar New Materialism, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Rice Seminar February conference, 2014-02-22-2014-02-23 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Zammito Ellen Zweig Rice Seminar Materialism cross disciplines, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Leibniz Society essay competition, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Leibniz Society essay competition, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Leibniz Society essay competition, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Leibniz Society essay competition, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Leibniz Society essay competition, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 22-25)
    - Leibniz Society, 1996-1999-05-24 (Box 6, Folder 26-29)
    - Leibniz Society essay competition, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 30-34)
    - Leibniz Society essay competition, 2006-2008 (Box 7, Folder 1-5)
    - Leibniz Society essay competition, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
    - Submission for Leibniz Society essay competition (Box 7, Folder 8-9)
    - Essay competition announcements (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - New G.W. Leibniz gesellschaft (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Old GWL gesellschaft (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Leibniz Society, old preparation papers for newsletter (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Leibniz Society newsletters (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence W/ A.P.A. + Journals about Leibniz Society (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - G.W. Leibniz- gesellschaft (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Leibniz Society essay competition (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Newsletters, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Leibniz Society Board packet Executive Committee file, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Leibniz Society constitutions, 1982-03-12 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - File to take to 1982 A.P.A meeting for Executive Committee meeting (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Leibniz Society Executive Committee, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Leibniz Society annual meeting, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Elliot Trina APA Leibniz Society Lois from Kel Philosophy University of Colorado, 1980-1986 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - R.M. Adams "Form + Matter in Leibniz" Leibniz Society Eastern APA, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Leibniz Society membership (Box 7, Folder 26-32)
    - President's correspondence (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Jan Covers VP Files (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Robert Adams "Leibniz's Theories of Contigency" (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Minutes annual meetings (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Papers from Sleigh (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - 17th Annual Leibniz Society (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Erster International Kongress, 2007-03-26-2007-03-30 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - US Leibniz Congress (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - So. American Leibniz Conference and Leibniz Society (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Leibniz Association (Engl.) (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Leibniz Society (Box 7, Folder 43,44)
    - South- Central Society for 18th Century Studies (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Societe Americaine de Philsophia de langue Francaise (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - American Philsophical Association (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Houston Philsophical Society (Box 7, Folder 48,49)
    - Mellon Workshop (Box 7, Folder 50,51)
    - Mellon follow-up meeting, Double Tree Hotel, New Orleans (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Meeting for Mellon Summer Institute (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Mellon agenda (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Mellon workshop, 1988-05-15-1988-05-27 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Correspodence about workshops (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Mellon workshop evaluations (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Mellon seminar (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Mellon seminar Ssmmer application correspondence (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Mellon seminar file (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Mellon seminar readings (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Tenure review correspondence (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Steven Crowell 308 Spring (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Nick Jolley's "A Study of the New Essays on Human Understanding" (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - R. Savage tenure materials (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - M. Murray tenure materials (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - C.Wilson's book (partial) (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Susanna G. tenure (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Memphis Consc. conference correspondence, 1982-10-07-1982-10-09 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Locke- Leibniz conference / Rice, 1982-11-15-1982-11-16 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Toronto conference, 1982-11-19-1982-11-21 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Philosophy Club talk, 1983-09-26 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Clear Lake lecture, 1983-03 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Scientia Colloquia, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 22-23)
    - Leibniz Congress, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Philosophy Club Talk ' Descartes and Newton, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Tsanoff conference paper, 1988-04-22 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - San Descartes conference, 1988-04 (Box 8)
    - Colloquia+ confs. Brown, 1988-1990 (Box 8, Folder 27,28)
    - 5th International LZ, Leibniz Congress, 1988-11-14-1988-11-19 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Leibniz Conference in Madrid, 1989-09-20-1989-09-22 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Iowa, 1989-04 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Buenos Aires Conference, 1989-11-20-1989-11-24 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Wisconsin conference, 1990-04-20-1990-04-22 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Big Fall ethics conference, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - History of Philsophy conferences, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 35-37)
    - Conference History of Philosophy, 1991-04-19-1991-04-20 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Oregon State conference, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Midwest conference, 1992-05-02-1995-05-03 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Vltn Leibniz Congres address, etc, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Midwest Early Modern UCH, 1994-03-12-1994-03-13 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Rome Conference, 1996-10-03-1996-10-05 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Young Leibniz Conference, 1996-10-18-1996-10-20 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Leibniz, Monism + Mercer Presentation U Mass, 1996-12-05 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - U Mass Conference Women in Philosophy 17th Century, 1997-11-07-1997-11-09 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Sleigh Brown, 1988 (Box 8)
    - A Short History of the Leibniz Society of North America by Mark A. Kulstad
  - Lectures and Conferences, 1998-2016 (Box 9-11)
    - Woburn Conference Young Lebiniz L,5, Tech: Multiple World, 1998-01-02 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Toronto Problem of Evil conference, 1999-09-03-1999-09-05 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Gulf Coast conference in Early Modern Philosophy, 1999-03-20-1999-03-21 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Toronto Evil Conference and Anthology, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Denver conference: Inter Mountain Seminar. and WY, 1999-04-24-1999-04-26 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Turku Finland, Force and Will in 17th C., 1999-08-12-1999-08-14 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Madison conference (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Left-over papers from Rice conferences + Lectures (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Tsanoff Intro; Collog Misc. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - California State University conference (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Duke conference (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Innateness debate Eric and Mark (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Misc conference (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Pragmatism seminar (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Germany (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Cerisy Page PFS (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Midwest seminar (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - So. Central Sec. for 18th C. studies (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Lebiniz conferences (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Sleigh's handout (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Maragaret Wilson conference, Grafton VT (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - "Leibniz and the English speaking world," University of Liverpool (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Duke conference (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - History of Philosophy conferences, 2000-09-21-2003-04 (Box 9, Folder 24-32)
    - History of Philosophy conferences, 2003-04-03-2004 (Box 10, Folder 1-6)
    - History of Philosophy conferences, 2004-2007-05-15 (Box 10, Folder 7-24)
    - Toland Stuart Brown conference, 2007-06 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Princeton Leibniz- Spinoza conference, 2007-09-28-2007-09-30 (Box 10, Folder 26,27)
    - Granada Leibniz, 2007-10 (Box 10, Folder 28,29)
    - Montreal NE colloquium handouts + paper (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - University of Paris -X WE/LEIBNIZ/NE Ho's + paper (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - MAK Paris- X NE paper (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - History of Philsophy conferences, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 33-37)
    - History of Philosophy conference, 2009-09-25-2016-02 (Box 11, Folder 1-18)
    - Overvold conference (Box 11, Folder 19)